Has the Xingyun Ranking been released?
My lady, your foresight is impeccable.
Those girls
heard that Cheng Qi got married
and stopped buying books.
Mr. Ling also heard the rumors
and started buying books by the box.
Cheng Qi is about to fall off the Xingyun Ranking.
Did you make sure
the bookshop knows?
As you ordered,
his books can only
be bought by the box.
Let's see how far he can go.
I want him to know
that only I can
give him what he wants.
Tell everyone,
if he comes to see me,
bring him straight to me.
Yes.
Serve the meal.
I'm full.
I'll take my leave now.
Take your time.
What happened?
My lord, you made your son-in-law angry.
Everyone's been scrambling for books today.
I grabbed 500.
Not sure if it's enough for the Star Chart.
Who told you to buy books?
Wasn't it your note?
I told you not to take shortcuts.
But you said you wanted to be the top.
I want to be the top,
but with my own strength.
What I'm doing now
is no different from them.
Cheng Qi,
I don't understand your rules.
But you said
you like to write down the moving
and warm emotions in life,
and compile them into a book,
so that more people can see hope
and beauty,
and overcome the setbacks in life.
But if I don't make it into the top ten,
how can I let others see it?
My dear,
there's no need to do that.
At worst,
just don't let so many people see it.
It's unnecessary.
You think I'm making a fuss?
No.
My lady.
I...
Go return these books yourself.
What are you waiting for?
Move them now,
or I'll throw them away.
My lady.
Don't throw away the books.
They are quite expensive.
How about you hit me?
It's embarrassing for you to get up.
If you don't throw the books,
I'll get up.
Who wants to hit you?
I'm already tired of escorting every day.
Alright, my dear.
Don't be upset.
Actually,
when preparing for the Starry Night,
I was very confident.
But I found
what I did was useless.
So I was frustrated.
I was very surprised to see
the booklets you bought for me.
But I was also angry at myself for being useless.
So I said something stupid.
Please don't mind.
And
I'll earn back the money
I spent on the album.
You don't have to.
700 taels!
Tell me in front of
the whole family,
what did you spend it on?
Buying books.
You're still reading books?
It's so ridiculous!
I spent dozens of taels on wine,
you were already pushing me around.
Now you've spent so much money,
what do you have to say?
Jiaojiao,
what's going on?
You've always been frugal,
how could you spend so much money?
How can you be so reckless
and still want to manage the household?
Dad,
you should be the judge.
It's not her fault.
I borrowed the money.
I'll pay it back to the agency as soon as possible.
With your salary,
do you plan to take ten years
or eight years?
I'll pay it back
within a month.
If you can't pay it back,
what should we do?
If he can't repay,
I...
I'll give up the position.
Uncle,
is that okay?
Whoever takes over
must follow the rules of the agency.
This matter
is up to my father.
Dad,
I think it's fine.
This month,
Jiaojiao will take over the escort agency.
Li Shi,
hand over your men to her.
But,
Dad,
it's them who owe money,
not me.
They are also members of the escort agency.
If they owe money,
it's the agency that owes money.
The whole agency should help.
It's better than letting those escorts be idle.
I admire your generosity.
Besides,
Uncle,
the escort business in this city has been in a slump.
It really needs to be reorganized.
I...
It was Cheng Qi
who brought in new business for the agency.
He must have a way.
You...
I'm willing to help them pay back the money.
I won't take
this month's escort fee.
And me, and me.
I won't take this month's escort fee either.
You...
It's settled then.
Get to work.
What's going on with this list?
Cheng Qi had already fallen out of
the top ten of the Nebula List.
But yesterday, Su came straight to the store
and bought 500 copies.
So...
How are you handling things?
Didn't you understand why you weren't
allowed to buy Cheng Qi's book?
This is no small amount of money.
Su Yuejiao
is willing to do this for him.
My Lady,
why don't we just change the list?
After all, only we know how many they bought.
Just post the list as usual.
Yes, My Lady.
If anything goes wrong again,
you won't have to stay at the bookshop anymore.
Yes, My Lady.
My Lady, are you planning to help Cheng Qi?
This way,
it's actually more interesting.
I want to see
how far he can go.
From now on,
anyone who buys a booklet of Cheng Qi's poems
can enjoy three free escorts
in the Imperial City with the silk.
Valid for the month.
Three escorts in the city
are not worth a book.
Will it work?
We'll know if we try.
But
these 1,000 books
are 1,000 certificates.
Do we have to
copy them one by one?
Tell me.
What do you want to engrave?
Thank you for your help.
I'm doing this for my sister,
not for you.
If it affects Jiaojiao's seal,
I won't forgive you.
Yes, yes.
You're the best in the capital.
And Tang Xin cherishes
your pick very much.
This is carved wood.
Dip it in ink and cover it on the silk paper.
Then you don't have to copy it word by word.
This way, the time cost is greatly reduced.
I didn't expect you to be so thoughtful
in doing things.
Did you
plan it all out already?
I started thinking as soon as
I saw those books.
Because you trust me,
I'll do my best.
I have some of my poetry books in the Moon God Pavilion.
We can sell them with the novels.
If it goes well,
we'll see results in half a month.
If the clients like our escort service,
we can offer them
a buy-one-get-one-free deal,
which will double our orders.
Alright,
let's do it your way.
I'll go ask my grandpa for the seal.
It's already in the yard.
Take it, Mr. Su.
What
are these books?
They're for you.
No charge?
Then I dare not read them.
As you wish.
You can give the money you earn
from selling these novels to Cheng Yicheng.
Cheng Qi,
did you sell Cheng Yicheng to her?
I only sell, I don't buy.
He insisted on dedicating himself to her.
I have no choice.
Congratulations.
This book is a gift for your congratulations.
My lady,
are you reading?
Don't make noise.
Whose book is it
that can make you change?
I need to learn from it.
So you don't feel sleepy when reading?
It's strange.
I'm not sleepy when I read this.
The words are a little weak,
but it's interesting.
But I always feel
this story is familiar.
Maybe
all loving couples are the same.
If they really divorced,
they would be laughed at.
Well,
if you divorce me,
would you be afraid of being made a joke of?
I...
Who dares?
Who's there?
What are you listening to here?
My Lord
I... I just came here.
I didn't hear anything.
Don't come here at noon.
Do you hear me?
At noon.
I remember it.
Little escort.
Don't let anyone disturb them after noon
so that they can be alone.
They must have feelings for each other.
When can I open the door?
Here you are.
Thank you.
Here.
It's so pretty.
Thank you.
Take it.
How's it going?
Finished giving out over there?
Smooth.
Keep going.
There's even a surplus.
Impossible.
You did the accounting yourself.
It's not even a month.
How did we get so many new clients?
Thanks to the books
you bought earlier.
We let them try our escort service
almost for free.
And you've set strict rules
requiring all escorts to treat every order,
no matter how small, with care.
Once merchants use our services,
they naturally see us as reliable,
and become repeat customers.
So this time,
we're riding the wave of the Xingyun Convention.
It's your foresight
and planning that made it happen.
Actually,
I've also benefited from our escort agency,
And thanks to my invention,
the wooden copying machine.
In that case,
Jiaojiao, you should take over
the escort agency earlier.
Jiaojiao
Come here.
The Escort Agency is thriving.
In the future,
there must be a daughter to inherit it.
Now that you have such a good son-in-law,
you should start a family as soon as possible.
Grandpa,
what are you talking about?
My Lord,
I didn't lie to you, did I?
They really need people.
My Lord,
we've been working
in the capital for so long.
But no one has ever treated us as human beings.
Why can't we be hired
by the Escort Agency?
We are bandits.
If we have a chance to make a living,
who would like to be a bandit?
Can't we
have a chance to start over?
This is the money from selling the booklet.
After deducting the agency's expenses and the cost of the book,
this is what's left.
Here you are.
This is the commission of the book.
All here.
Here you are.
This is your money.
Why do you give it to me?
You are my wife.
Of course, I should give it to you.
Take it.
I have such a good son-in-law.
I should have a baby as soon as possible.
I didn't expect
these storybooks could sell for so much money.
How about it?
I'm smart, right?
Thanks to that unknown little book.
Why don't you praise my songbook?
Mainly because your writing is too literary.
No.
I mean,
you helped me silence my uncle this time.
Tell me,
what do you want?
I'll do anything for you.
Anything?
How about
we start a family?
Don't even think about it!
I'm not having a family with you!
What are you thinking?
My lady, where did your mind go?
I'm warning you,
if you dare to do something wrong,
I...
I won't be nice to you.
My dear,
I want you to write the final words for me.
Which eye of yours
thinks I can write?
I mean,
I'll read it,
and you can change it if you don't like it.
To be honest,
I think your speech is good,
but I don't really understand it.
Then I'll keep changing it until you do.
Why does it sound
like you're not serious?
Just tell me yes or no.
♪Smooth face with painted eyebrows♪
♪Orioles sing and swallows dance♪
♪Lightly brushed♪
♪The fragrance lingers in the bridal chamber♪
♪Last night's whispers were filled with longing♪
The silver candle flickered and swayed.
Why does it feel a bit improper?
Then I'll change to another one.
Clouds, trees, and sandy embankment.
Willows and small bridges.
The market is lined with pearls and jewels, reflecting the bright moon.
The red canopy exudes fragrance.
Phoenix curtains and silk screens.
Silk fills the house, intoxicating the world.
Okay, I'll try another one.
The moonlight shines for years.
The waves are endless.
The sky is high, clouds light, rain fine.
Missing you day and night.
Jiao,
I can't hold on.
I can't help you.
I'll go escort the goods first.
Why has business in this city decreased so much?
It's all been taken over by the Su family.
The Sus?
Su Liwei
is getting bold.
It must be
the idea of that matrilocal man.
He's selling his books
with free escorts.
Many merchants find it attractive
and went to him.
Why don't you do the same?
and give away something?
I did.
And I even paid extra to hire some managers back.
But I lost more and more money.
Where has Su Li been recently?
He's either at the casino or at Huayue Tower every day.
Let's go and see him.
Come on.
Waiter.
Mr. Su.
Fifty taels.
Please pay first.
What do you mean?
I just sat down.
I haven't ordered anything yet.
You want me to pay?
The Old Master said
you need to pay
for the drinks in advance.
Well, I won't eat here.
Fifty taels.
Stealing my business, huh?
How dare you!
Well,
I'm not doing anything right now.
You lost your money?
Yeah.
If I could steal your business,
I would have done it long ago.
Mr. Fu,
do you still need people?
Take me in.
If you still have the Su's Escort Agency,
I can think about it.
But now,
I think you'd better forget it.
I don't want to go there.
That girl should
take all your business.
Gong Xi, Fa Cai.
My son-in-law,
I have a question for you.
How did you write this script?
My dear,
do you think it's not good?
Simple and easy to understand.
I'm not as good as him.
Some plots are written by him according to my idea.
No wonder some parts
are simple and plain.
My dear, are you praising
or cursing me?
What else does your boss like to read
except for scripts?
She doesn't read
any type of book.
Because she grew up escorting with her mom.
She took over the Escort Agency at a young age.
So
she's not interested in anything except escorting.
But why
do you write scripts?
Because I was young when I came here.
My Lord knew I wanted to study,
so she hired a teacher to teach us.
She said as long as we were willing to learn,
she would help us.
It seems she didn't attend the class.
I did.
But I slept too deeply
and was kicked out by the teacher.
Go, my son-in-law.
Wait for me.
I need to think of another way.
My lady, this is the novel from the escort agency.
It sells well in Yunjing.
It's all about the married couples.
So vulgar.
Did Zhang Qijia go to the City of Diamond recently?
Yes.
I heard that the young master took some young masters with him.
He probably won't be back before the final exam.
Then let's make it quick.
Post the list today.
For the banquet,
let them bring their families.
I'll get it done right away.
The Starry Night Gala final is in seven days.
[There will be two rounds.]
[The first round is the flying flower order.]
[The theme will be announced on the spot.]
[The final round is the poetry gathering.]
[The theme is the prosperity of the Yun State.]
[The form is not limited.]
[You can invite performers.]
Time to eat.
I'm starving.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Everyone's here.
Let's eat.
Wait.
Guys,
I need your help.
We're family.
Just say it.
You all have been around the country,
and seen a lot.
Could you tell me the happiest
and most joyful thing in the Yun State?
What?
Happiness?
Just tell Cheng Qi
the happy things you've met
in your escort years.
Happy things.
Zhen,
when I was pregnant with Yu'er,
I had braised pork from Huayue Restaurant for the first time.
I was so happy
that I kissed Su.
It turns out that the braised pork Grandpa loves
is not just a dish,
but your memory.
Later, this Yunjing
changed too fast.
Things and people are different.
Even the owner of Huayue Tower has changed.
But that night
was the happiest time of my life.
However,
this house is getting bigger and bigger,
but without Zhen,
it feels empty.
Empty?
I can't even find a place to put more carriages.
No romance.
It's my turn.
I'm happiest
when
Tang Xin smiles at me.
I...
With a whip in hand,
I can do anything.
Speed and passion
are the source of my happiness every day.
There are more and more young ladies selling rouge.
I mean, there are more escorts delivering rouge.
There are also cakes and fruits.
I enjoy escorting these.
The happiest moment
is when I see the clients
showing their gratitude after each escort.
And also,
when my parents escorted goods with me.
Is the final exam really that difficult?
Maybe I should
ask around tomorrow.
No need.
I'll think about it.
What...
What's going on?
I'm really stuck right now.
My dear,
why don't you have a drink with me?
I...
I won't drink.
Maybe after you take a sip,
I'll suddenly get an idea.
What idea?
It's just an excuse for your drinking.
Come on, please.
Please.
Any ideas yet?
Want another drink?
Jiao.
Jiao, you didn't drink much.
How come you're so drunk?
Jiao also wants to escort to Klak City.
Where are you going?
Go to bed.
Why is your face so red?
Are you having a fever?
Mom.
Look.
There's a juggler.
Mom.
Is this my mom?
That storyteller
is not as good as Cheng Qi.
Who is Cheng Qi?
Cheng Qi
is the best storyteller
in the entire Yun State.
Is he that good in your heart?
There's a light in his eyes.
And just like you,
he also calls me Jiao.
He...
is very important to you.
Mom,
look,
those Lang Yue people
are dancing.
They look so happy.
Let's go dance too.
Alright.
Jiao has grown taller.
The dress is too short.
Can I be an escort now?
Do you like being an escort?
I want to be like you.
I hope
Jiao can do what she wants to do.
Even if it's just peace and joy,
it's also good.
I like being an escort.
Every time I see the client
receiving the expected items
and meeting the person they want to see,
I feel happy too.
Just like Cheng Qi,
who loves writing lyrics,
he doesn't find it hard at all.
Jiao, be good.
Stay here.
I'll be back soon.
Mom,
come back soon.
why haven't you come back?